[Description] The presenter appears on screen in front of the game Hogwarts Legacy. He starts speaking in an animated tone.
[説明] プレゼンターは画面に登場し、ゲーム『ホグワーツ・レガシー』の前に立っています。元気なトーンで話し始めます。
[Description] In the game, the character casts the Revelio spell. Bright objects with question mark symbols appear.
[説明] ゲーム内で、キャラクターは「レヴェリオ」呪文を唱えます。疑問符のついた明るいオブジェクトが現れます。
[Description] The character moves through different rooms in search of the objects.
[説明] キャラクターはオブジェクトを探して、さまざまな部屋を移動します。
[Description] The character approaches a mysterious door and presses a button to display a sequence of numbers and symbols.
[説明] キャラクターは謎めいた扉に近づき、ボタンを押して数字と記号のシーケンスを表示します。
[Description] The numbers 5 and 12 appear on the door's mechanism.
[説明] 扉のメカニズムに5と12の数字が表示されます。
[Description] The presenter zooms in on the door to explain the number puzzle.
[説明] プレゼンターは扉をズームインして、数字のパズルを説明します。
[Description] A triangle with numbers and symbols at its vertices appears on the screen.
[説明] 画面には、頂点に数字と記号が表示された三角形が表示されます。
[Description] A guide is shown with the game's symbols and their corresponding numerical values from 0 to 9.
[説明] ゲームの記号と、それぞれの数値（0から9）が対応しているガイドが表示されます。
[Description] The presenter points to the symbols and explains how values are assigned to each.
[説明] プレゼンターは記号を指さし、それぞれに数値がどのように割り当てられるかを説明します。
[Description] The first puzzle is solved by adding the values: 3 + 0 + 2.
[説明] 最初のパズルは、3 + 0 + 2という値を足すことで解決されます。
[Description] A symbol in the shape of a goat is selected as the answer.
[説明] 山羊の形をした記号が答えとして選ばれます。
[Description] The cursor highlights the symbols in order: 0, 1, 2.
[説明] カーソルは記号を順番に指し示します：0、1、2。
[Description] It is confirmed that the sum matches the target number.
[説明] 合計が目標の数字と一致することが確認されます。
[Description] The character spins the object with a question mark and selects the correct symbol.
[説明] キャラクターは疑問符のついたオブジェクトを回転させ、正しい記号を選びます。
[Description] The second puzzle is tackled, which results in the number 12.
[説明] 2番目のパズルに進み、その結果として12という数字が表示されます。
[Description] The cursor moves to the symbol already visible on the screen.
[説明] カーソルは、すでに画面に表示されている記号に移動します。
[Description] The symbol shown is the unicorn, identified as value 1.
[説明] 表示されている記号はユニコーンで、値は1です。
[Description] The presenter continues explaining the logic behind the puzzle.
[説明] プレゼンターはパズルの論理を引き続き説明します。
[Description] The values 1 + 4 + 7 are added, and the symbol in the shape of an octopus is selected.
[説明] 値1 + 4 + 7を足し、タコの形をした記号を選びます。
[Description] The character interacts with the second spinning object and picks the correct symbol.
[説明] キャラクターは2番目の回転するオブジェクトと対話し、正しい記号を選びます。
[Description] The character stands in front of the door and presses the button to open it.
[説明] キャラクターは扉の前に立ち、開けるためにボタンを押します。
[Description] The door slowly opens, revealing a secret room with a glowing chest inside.
[説明] 扉がゆっくりと開き、内部に輝く宝箱がある秘密の部屋が現れます。